[upbeat rock music]
活泼的摇滚音乐
- How about these American flag earrings?
这些美国国旗耳环怎么样？
Do these say Spirit of Independent school recital?
这些能表达独立学校音乐会的精神吗？
- Oh, totally.
哦，当然可以。
Oh, hey, what about these magnetic earrings?
哦，嘿，这些磁性耳环呢？
Do they say, "I'm super lame
它们是不是在说：“我超级无趣，因为还没打耳洞？”
'cause I don't have my ears pierced yet?"
[笑声] - 一语中的。
[laughter] - Nailed it.
[轻笑]
[chuckles]
道恩，没人看得出它们是假的。
- Dawn, no one can tell they're fake.
[重击声] - 这就告诉他们了。
[thuds]
- That'll tell 'em.
- 这会让他们明白的。
[laughter]
- Why won't they stay on?
- 为什么它们就是不掉下来？
- Oh, sweetie.
- 哦，亲爱的。
You've got some serious D.E.L.s.
你有一些严重的D.E.L.s。
- D.E.L.s?
- D.E.L.s？
- Dense earlobes. It's a thing.
- 厚耳垂。这是个问题。
That's why those magnets don't work for you.
这就是为什么那些磁铁对你不起作用。
And those shoes are questionable.
还有那些鞋子也值得怀疑。
[laughter]
笑声
- The shoes are fine...
- 鞋子没问题...
but those lobes are pretty meaty.
但那些耳垂真的很厚实。
[laughter]
笑声
- Do a lot of people have this?
- 很多人都有这个吗？
- Oh, goodness, I hope not.
- 哦，天哪，希望没有。
It must run in your family.
这一定是家族遗传。
- Nope.
- 不是。
- These magnets work just fine for us.
- 这些磁铁对我们来说很好用。
- I'm wearing five pairs.
- 我穿了五双。
[laughter]
[笑声]
- I hate that they look prettier than me.
- 我讨厌她们看起来比我漂亮。
- And the skinny one has better shoes.
- 而且那个瘦的鞋子更好看。
I just call it as I see it, girl.
我只是实话实说，女孩。
Sorry. [laughter]
对不起。[笑声]
♪ ♪
- Mom, Dad...
- 妈妈，爸爸...
it's time.
是时候了。
- Dawn, we've been over this.
- 道恩，我们讨论过这个。
We're not sending your brothers to live with your Aunt Jackie.
我们不会把你弟弟们送到你婶婶杰基那里去住。
- No! I meant it's finally time for me to get my ears pierced.
不！我是说终于到了我要打耳洞的时候了。
I mean, I really want to look nice for our school recital.
我是说，我真的想在我们学校的演出上看起来漂亮一点。
- Dawn, I still think you're too young.
Dawn，我还是觉得你太年轻了。
You can wear magnet earrings.
你可以戴磁铁耳环。
- No, I can't.
不，我不能。
- D.E.L.s. - You have them, too?
D.E.L.s. - 你也有吗？
- No, gross, ugh.
不，恶心，呃。
Your mother does.
你妈妈有。
[laughter] - We don't.
[笑声] - 我们没有。
- Totally normal.
完全正常。
- Nothing meaty over here.
这里没有肉食。
[laughter] - Come on, Mom.
拜托，妈妈。
- Sorry, we're just not a piercing family.
对不起，我们家不是穿孔家族。
- But Mae and all of my friends have theirs pierced.
但是梅和我的所有朋友都穿孔了。
- Honey, I don't even have my ears pierced.
亲爱的，我甚至没有穿耳洞。
- What? But I've seen you wear earrings.
什么？但我见过你戴耳环。
- On special occasions, we use the hot glue gun.
在特殊场合，我们使用热熔胶枪。
[laughter] Yes, we do. Yes, we do.
是的，我们确实。是的，我们确实。
- Ugh! This is so unfair!
啊！这太不公平了！
Thick lobes and a "no?" - Yeah, it's a tough day.
厚厚的耳垂和‘不行’？是啊，真是艰难的一天。
[laughter] - [exhales]
Well, you know what?
你知道吗？
One of those things I can do something about.
其中一件事我能有所作为。
I'm gonna get my ears pierced behind Mom and Dad's back.
我要背着爸妈去打耳洞。
Because it's time I declare my independence!
因为我宣布独立的时候到了！
- I admire your chutzpah, Dawn,
我佩服你的胆量，Dawn，
but you can't declare your independence without us.
但你不能在没有我们的情况下宣布独立。
- Yeah.
是啊。
- We're getting our ears pierced, too.
我们也要去打耳洞。
- No, we want our independence to be independent
不，我们希望我们的独立是独立的
of her independence.
与她的独立无关。
- What if I want to get my ears pierced?
- 如果我想打耳洞呢？
- Well, then, declare your own independence.
- 那么，就宣布你自己的独立。
- I don't want to be independent alone!
- 我不想一个人独立！
- Fine! We'll be independent together.
- 好吧！我们将一起独立。
Gentlemen...
先生们...
Mark your votes.
记下你们的投票。
- Wait, why do you have index cards on you?
- 等等，你们身上为什么带着索引卡？
- We vote a lot, Dawn.
- 我们经常投票，Dawn。
- Are you new here?
- 你是新来的吗？
[laughter]
- All right, let's see what we got.
- 好吧，让我们看看我们得到了什么。
Perfect.
完美。
"Get a snake" it is.
“买条蛇”就这么定了。
[laughter] - Snake?
I wrote, "get a snack."
我写的是“买点零食”。
I'm hungry. [laughter]
我饿了。
- Well, you misspelled "snack" and wrote "snake,"
- 好吧，你把“snack”拼错了，写成了“snake”，
and since we've been asking Dad for one for years,
而且我们多年来一直向爸爸要一条蛇，
we're getting a snake.
我们要买条蛇了。
- Come on, guys, snakes really freak me out.
来吧，伙计们，蛇真的让我感到害怕。
- Then it is agreed.
那么，就这样定了。
Henceforth, today shall be known as our...
从今以后，今天将被我们称为...
"Quadpendence Day."
“四重独立日”。
[laughter] - To the mall!
去商场！
- Okay, hold up.
好吧，等等。
Does it really need a cute name?
它真的需要一个可爱的名字吗？
For once, can we just do something?
就这一次，我们能不能就做点什么？
- Fine. - No name.
好吧。
- [unenthused] To the mall.
去商场。
[laughter]
[笑声]
- Okay.
好吧。
- Who knew you needed a parent with you
谁会知道打耳洞需要家长陪同呢？
to get your ears pierced?
还有买蛇！
- And to get a snake!
这个计划从我们没给它起名时就注定要失败了。
- This plan was doomed when we didn't name it.
[笑声] 好吧，这正式...
[laughter] - Well, this officially...
[笑声] 上面写着，“袜子”。
[laughter] - That says, "socks."
对，我知道！
- Yeah, I know!
因为这味道...
Because it stinks...
像袜子。
like socks.
就像袜子一样。
[laughter] both: Oh.
[笑声] 两人: 哦。
[upbeat rock music]
[欢快的摇滚音乐]
♪ ♪
[音乐]
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na-na ♪ - ♪ Hey! ♪
- [音乐] ♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐呐 ♪ - [音乐] ♪ 嘿！ ♪
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na-na ♪ - ♪ One, two... ♪
- [音乐] ♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐呐 ♪ - [音乐] ♪ 一，二... ♪
- ♪ one-two-three-four! ♪
- [音乐] ♪ 一二三四！ ♪
♪ ♪
[音乐]
- I can't believe my plan to get my ears pierced didn't work.
- 我真不敢相信我打耳洞的计划没成功。
- Well, did you name the plan?
- 那你有给计划起名字吗？
You guys usually come up with a cute name.
你们通常会给计划起个可爱的名字。
[laughter] - No.
[笑声] - 没有。
Someone didn't want to.
有人不想起。
[laughter]
[笑声]
- That's why we didn't get a snake either.
- 所以我们也没弄到蛇。
- So much for our unnamed attempt at independence.
- 我们那次未命名的独立尝试就这样泡汤了。
[tuba note blares]
[大号音符响起]
- All right, kids. Let's rehearse.
- 好了，孩子们。我们来排练一下。
[baton taps] With feeling.
[指挥棒轻敲] 要有感情。
- Well, I'm not giving up.
- 嗯，我不会放弃的。
- "Yankee Doodle" me.
- 《扬基歌》我。
[laughter]
[笑声]
[playing "Yankee Doodle"]
[演奏《扬基歌》]
- Did our forefathers give up on their Independence Day?
- 我们的先辈在独立日放弃了吗？
No! They never gave up!
没有！他们从未放弃！
♪ ♪
- Where are my whistlers?
- 我的口哨手在哪里？
[whistling "Yankee Doodle"]
[口哨演奏《扬基歌》]
- They fought for their freedom,
- 他们为自由而战，
just like we need to fight for ours.
就像我们需要为我们的自由而战。
- Triangles!
- They fought for liberty and the pursuit of happiness.
Just like we need to fight for earrings,
and the pursuit of a snake.
So give me liberty, or give me death!
- Death? - Shh!
- We want a snake, but not that bad.
- You know what I mean!
We just need to find a way to get the things that we want.
- Snare drum.
[drum rolls]
all: Dooley!
大家：杜利！
- It's Yankee Dooley,
- 是扬基·杜利，
and I heard everything.
- 我全听到了。
I'll be outside your garage at 4:37 precisely.
- 我会在四点三十七分准时到你车库外。
[laughter]
When the coast is clear, signal me with a bird sound.
- 等周围没人了，用鸟叫声给我信号。
♪ ♪
- Then the day that we as Quads declare our independence...
- 那么，我们四胞胎宣布独立的日子……
is back on. - Or...
- 又回来了。 - 或者……
a shorter way to say it would be....
一个更简短的说法是...
- [sighs] Fine.
- [叹气] 好吧。
"Quadpendence Day" is back on.
“四重独立日”又回来了。
- And everybody!
- 还有大家！
[all playing "Yankee Doodle"]
[所有人演奏《扬基歌》]
♪ ♪
[upbeat rock music]
[欢快的摇滚音乐]
- Okay.
- 好的。
4:37.
37。
- I'll signal Dooley with the bird sound.
- 我会用鸟叫声给杜利发信号。
Bird sound! Bird sound! Bird sound!
鸟叫声！鸟叫声！鸟叫声！
- No, I'm pretty sure he meant:
- 不，我很确定他指的是：
ca-caw, ca-caw!
ca-caw, ca-caw！
- No, he meant something like this.
- 不，他指的是这样的。
[elaborate cawing]
[复杂的鸟叫声]
- Bird sound! Bird sound! - Ca-caw! Ca-caw!
- 鸟叫声！鸟叫声！ - Ca-caw！Ca-caw！
- [elaborate cawing]
- [复杂的鸟叫声]
- Bird sound! Bird sound! - Ca-caw! Ca-caw!
- 鸟叫声！鸟叫声！ - Ca-caw！Ca-caw！
- [elaborate cawing]
- [复杂的鸟叫声]
- You know what?
- 你知道吗？
This is my fault.
这是我的错。
I should've just said, "text me."
我应该直接说“给我发短信”就好了。
[boys continue making bird sounds]
[男孩们继续发出鸟叫声]
- Stop it!
——停！
- Oh, hey, my call worked.
——哦，嘿，我的电话起作用了。
- No, my call worked. - No, my call worked.
——不，是我的电话起作用了。——不，是我的电话。
- What are you saying? - No, it was my call!
——你在说什么？——不，是我打的电话！
[overlapping squabbling]
——[争吵重叠]
- Stop!
——停！
- Bird brains.
——笨蛋。
- So, did you come through?
- 所以，你成功了吗？
- Boom! One ear piercer.
- 砰！一只穿耳的。
- Yes! Thanks, Dooley.
- 是的！谢谢，杜利。
- So, is there a boom in there for us?
- 那对我们来说有砰的一声吗？
- This is a two-boom bag, baby.
- 这是一个两砰的袋子，宝贝。
Boom!
砰！
One snake. - Sweet!
一条蛇。 - 太棒了！
- Awesome! - Cool.
- 太棒了！ - 酷。
[laughter]
[笑声]
Look.
看。
- [screams] - Oh, heck no!
- [尖叫] - 哦，绝对不行！
- Dicky, get him away!
- 迪基，把他弄走！
Snake!
蛇！
- You guys are just scared 'cause you haven't met him.
- 你们只是害怕，因为你们还没见过他。
Dawn, Mae, meet...
道恩，梅，来见见...
I'm gonna go with Christopher.
我要叫他克里斯托弗。
- Dude, it's a snake.
- 伙计，那是一条蛇。
It should be Chrissssss-topher.
应该叫克里斯托弗（Chrissssss-topher）。
- I think you overdid it on the "S"s.
- 我觉得你在“S”上用得太多了。
- Who are you, the "S" police?
- 你是谁，“S”警察吗？
- There's no such thing.
- 没有这种事。
- Then why you all over my "S"?
- 那你为什么老盯着我这个“S”？
[laughter] - Okay.
[笑声] - 好吧。
Somebody please put that snake away
谁来把那条蛇拿走
so Mae can pierce my ears.
这样梅可以给我的耳朵打洞。
- Okay, let's do this.
- 好的，我们开始吧。
- Oh, wait.
- 哦，等等。
Is this gonna hurt? - No.
这会很疼吗？ - 不会。
- [straining] - Oh!
- [用力] - 哦！
- [screaming] Ow!
- [尖叫] 哎哟！
- Was that Dawn? - [groans]
- 那是Dawn吗？ - [呻吟]
Ah! That doesn't count!
啊！那不算！
Keep an eye on my sandwich.
帮我看着我的三明治。
[laughter]
[笑声]
- Ahh, I thought you said that wasn't gonna hurt.
- 啊，我以为你说过那不会疼的。
- Sometimes I'm wrong.
- 有时候我也会错。
[laughter]
[笑声]
- Kids, what's going on? - We heard Dawn scream.
- 孩子们，发生什么事了？ - 我们听到Dawn尖叫了。
all: Oh.
大家：哦。
- That--that's just 'cause we were having a...
- 那——那只是因为我们正在进行一个...
"who-could-scream-the-loudest contest"?
- Yup. - Yes.
- Do you really expect us to believe you were having a
"who-could-scream-the-loudest contest"?
[laughter] - Without including me?
I want in! - [chuckles]
- Here we go. [clears throat]
- Oh, hey, Dicky!
What are you doing?
- Just trying to hurt myself so I'll scream louder.
[laughter] - Nice plan.
好计划。
- Dad, wait! [laughter]
爸，等等！
We should probably take this inside, right?
我们可能应该进屋里去，对吧？
- Oh, yeah, the acoustics.
哦，对，音响效果。
They're much better in there. - Ah, good thinking.
在里面好多了。
Clear the runway. [exhales]
好主意。
[laughter] Whoo!
清理跑道。
- [screams]
哇！
- You win, Dad! [nervous chuckles]
你赢了，爸爸！
- Chrissssss-topher tickles.
克里斯托弗挠痒痒。
[laughter]
哈哈哈
♪ ♪
[upbeat rock music]
[欢快的摇滚音乐]
- No way!
- 不可能！
- You really got your ears pierced?
- 你真的打了耳洞？
- Check 'em out, ladies.
- 看看这些，女士们。
- So cute!
- 太可爱了！
- So cute.
- 真可爱。
- Seriously? You guys got a snake?
- 真的吗？你们养了条蛇？
- Yup. - We sure did.
- 是的。 - 确实养了。
- Pretty awesome, huh?
- 很酷吧？
- Really? 'Cause you guys don't look like snake guys.
- 真的吗？你们看起来不像养蛇的人。
- Zip it, Franco. [laughter]
- 闭嘴，弗兰科。[笑声]
We're snake guys. His name's Christopher.
我们是养蛇的。它叫克里斯托弗。
[laughter]
[笑声]
- That doesn't even sound like a snake name.
- 那听起来根本不像蛇的名字。
- Zip it, Franco. That's because he said it wrong.
- 闭嘴，弗兰科。那是因为他说错了。
It's Chrissssss-topher.
是克里斯sssss-托弗。
[laughter] - I don't know.
[笑声] - 我不知道。
Sounds like you guys are just making this all up.
听起来你们好像在编故事。
- Zip it, Franco! [laughter]
- 闭嘴，弗兰科！[笑声]
- So how'd you get perst without a pernt?
- 那你是怎么得到‘perst’而没有‘pernt’的？
- "Pierced" without a "parent."
- ‘Pierced’（穿孔）没有‘parent’（父母）。
[laughter] - Oh.
[笑声] - 哦。
Dooley got me an ear piercer.
杜利给我弄了个耳洞穿孔器。
- That's supes kewl.
- 那真是超级酷。
- Thanks. [chuckles]
- 谢谢。[轻笑]
That is supes cool.
那真是超级酷。
- No, she said that soup is cold.
- 不，她说那汤是冷的。
[laughter]
[笑声]
- Oh, but it's supes cool that we all have our ears pierced.
哦，但我们都有耳洞真的很酷。
Right?
对吧？
- I have a confession.
我有个坦白。
- Wait, those-- those were just magnets?
等等，那些——那些只是磁铁？
- I'm sorry. I was faking it.
对不起，我一直在假装。
I was just so embarrassed my parents wouldn't let me
我只是太尴尬了，因为我的父母不允许我
get my ears pierced.
打耳洞。
- Mine wouldn't either.
我的父母也不会允许。
- Sam herr. [laughter]
山姆，天哪。
- I can't believe you guys were faking it.
真不敢相信你们都在假装。
- Dawn, you need to pierce our ears.
- 黎明，你得给我们打耳洞。
- Actually, I just have the piercer.
- 实际上，我只有打耳洞的工具。
Mae did the piercings.
梅做了打耳洞的事。
- Mae, you need to pierce our ears.
- 梅，你得给我们打耳洞。
- Yeah. - Tote-lay.
- 是的。
[laughter]
[笑声]
- Okay. I can handle those.
- 好吧。我能处理这些。
all: Yay!
大家：耶！
- Chrissssss-topher is real!
- 克里斯托弗是真的！
- I'm still not buying it.
- 我还是不信。
- Zip it, Franco! - Telling me to zip it
- 闭嘴，弗兰科！ - 让我闭嘴
doesn't prove you have a snake.
并不能证明你有蛇。
- You're right, so come to our house and we'll prove it.
- 你说得对，那就来我们家，我们会证明给你看。
- Oh, yeah? What time?
- 哦，是吗？什么时候？
- When the big hand's on three and the little hand's on...
- 当长针指向三，短针指向...
zip it! [laughter]
闭嘴！[笑声]
- I don't know what time that-- Harper boys: Zip it, Franco!
- 我不知道那个时间-- 哈珀兄弟：闭嘴，弗兰科！
[laughter]
[笑声]
♪ ♪
- Who are all these people?
- 这些人都是谁？
- I told a few guys.
- 我跟几个人说了。
- A few?
- 几个？
This is why we always tell you to zip it, Franco.
这就是为什么我们总是叫你闭嘴，弗兰科。
[laughter]
[笑声]
- Hey, where's the ear piercer?
- 嘿，穿耳器在哪儿？
- In the bag with the snake.
- 和蛇一起在包里。
[laughter] - Eww!
[笑声] - 哎呀！
- Is that sanitary?
- 那卫生吗？
- Well, Dooley had it in there before, and you're fine.
- 嗯，杜利之前把它放在那里，你也没事。
- Okay, as you all know, there were some doubters
- 好吧，大家都知道，有些人怀疑
as to whether or not we actually had a snake.
关于我们是否真的有一条蛇，有些人表示怀疑。
[laughter]
Nicky... - Well, boys...
Nicky... - 好吧，男孩们...
The time has come for you to--
现在是你们自己——
chat amongst yourselves. [laughter]
互相交流的时候了。
Boys, we need to chat amongst ourselves.
男孩们，我们需要互相交流一下。
[laughter]
- What? - Little problem.
什么？ - 小问题。
Christopher's missing! - What?
Christopher失踪了！ - 什么？
What do you mean, "missing?" - I-I think he means
你说的'失踪'是什么意思？ - 我想他的意思是
missssss-ing.
失踪了。
[laughter] - He must've escaped!
[笑声] - 他一定是逃走了！
- What do you mean, "escaped?" - I think he means...
- 你说的'逃走'是什么意思？ - 我想他指的是...
essssss-caped!
逃走了！
[laughter] - Don't tell Dawn,
[笑声] - 别告诉Dawn，
or she's gonna freak out.
否则她会发疯的。
- Uh...what's going on?
- 呃...发生了什么？
Quad boys: Nothing!
四兄弟：没什么！
- Then why are you whispering?
- 那你们为什么在窃窃私语？
- [stammers] Why are you whispering?
- [结巴] 你为什么在窃窃私语？
- I'm whispering because you're whispering.
- 我小声说话是因为你在小声说话。
- We're whispering because we don't want you to hear that
- 我们小声说话是因为不想让你听到
we lost the snake. both: Dicky!
我们把蛇弄丢了。两人: Dicky!
- Sorry!
- 对不起！
I meant lossssss-t. - [laughter]
我的意思是丢sssss-了。- [笑声]
- Don't freak out.
- 别慌。
- Oh, I'm freaking out.
- 哦，我慌了。
- Me too!
- 我也是！
[laughter]
[笑声]
- Hey, guys! What's the hold up?
- 嘿，伙计们！怎么停下了？
- Yeah, Dawn. What's the hold up?
是的，Dawn。怎么回事？
- And what's with that fahn-say footwork?
还有，那套花哨的舞步是怎么回事？
[laughter]
（笑声）
- Oh, you know! [nervous chuckles]
哦，你知道的！（紧张的笑声）
Just...
只是...
super excited to pierce your ears.
超级兴奋要给你们打耳洞。
- I can't do this.
我做不到。
My hands are shaking.
我的手在发抖。
- Relax, I'll do the piercings.
放松，我来打耳洞。
- And I'll handle the guys. - And I'll search for the snake.
我会处理那些家伙。 - 我会去找那条蛇。
- All right, ladies.
好的，女士们。
Who's up first?
谁先来？
[laughter]
[笑声]
- So, here's the thing.
那么，事情是这样的。
You can't see the snake right now because he's shedding,
你现在看不到蛇，因为它正在蜕皮，
and wants some privacy.
想要一些隐私。
- Snakes don't need privacy.
蛇不需要隐私。
- Told you they didn't have a snake. I'm out of here!
我告诉过你们他们没有蛇。我要走了！
Oh, and before you say it,
哦，在你们说之前，
let me say it for you.
让我替你们说。
both: Zip it, Franco!
都闭嘴，弗兰科！
- We say where the "zip its" go, Franco.
- 我们决定哪里需要‘闭嘴’，弗兰科。
[laughter]
[笑声]
♪ ♪
- Oh, look at you, Miss Dense Lobes.
- 哦，看看你，浓耳垂小姐。
Shopping for real earrings.
在挑选真正的耳环。
Such a dreamer.
真是个梦想家。
[laughter] - I don't have to dream anymore.
[笑声] - 我不再需要做梦了。
Ka-pow! - Ka-wow!
咔-砰！ - 咔-哇！
You sneaky little minx.
你这个狡猾的小妖精。
- We're all sneaky little minxes.
- 我们都是狡猾的小妖精。
together: Ka-pow! [laughter]
- 一起：咔-砰！[笑声]
- Oh, Tom, look at her dreaming.
- 哦，汤姆，看她在做梦。
She wants her ears pierced so badly.
- 她非常想打耳洞。
- Yup.
- 是的。
And you still won't let her.
- 但你还是不让她打。
What? You won't! [laughter]
- 什么？你不让她打！[笑声]
- All because I'm afraid to get my ears pierced.
- 就因为我害怕打耳洞。
Am I a horrible parent?
- 我是个糟糕的父母吗？
- Yes. [laughter]
- 是的。[笑声]
[stammers] No worse than me.
[结巴] 不比我差。
Not getting the boys a snake because I'm afraid.
不给孩子们买蛇是因为我害怕。
- Well, you know what?
- 你知道吗？
Our horrible parenting ends today.
我们糟糕的育儿今天就结束。
- All of it? - Oh, no!
- 全部？ - 哦，不！
Just this part! - Ah! Are you sure?
就这部分！ - 啊！你确定吗？
The boys taking care of a snake?
孩子们照顾一条蛇？
- Come on. - No, you're right.
- 来吧。 - 不，你说得对。
I'm sure they can handle it.
我确信他们能应付。
[squeamish groan]
[厌恶的呻吟]
♪ ♪
- Where could he be? We've searched everywhere!
- 他在哪儿？我们到处都找过了！
[phone dings]
[手机叮的一声]
- Well, this is just wonderful!
- 哦，这真是太好了！
Franco text blasted that we're liars.
弗兰科发短信说我们是骗子。
We need to find that snake.
我们需要找到那条蛇。
- Oh, there he is!
- 哦，他在那儿！
- Hey! That's my leg!
- 嘿！那是我的腿！
[laughter] - Dude...
[笑声] - 伙计...
You gotta eat more. [laughter]
你得多吃点。[笑声]
♪ ♪
- Oh! How do these look?
- 哦！这些看起来怎么样？
- Like...
- 像是...
your mother! - Oh, that's the last thing
- 你妈妈！ - 哦，我最不想做的就是看起来像——
I want to do is to look like-- - Your mother!
- 你妈妈！
- That's what I'm saying...
- 我说的就是这个...
Mother! [laughter]
- 妈妈！
Hi, Mom. Whatcha doing?
- 嗨，妈妈。你在做什么？
I'm just over here looking "ear-resistible."
- 我就在这儿，看起来“耳不可挡”。
- Aw, Dawn, I know exactly why you're here.
- 噢，Dawn，我知道你为什么来这里。
- You do?
你知道？
- Yeah, you're checking out the real earrings because
是的，你在看真正的耳环，因为
you want your ears pierced so badly!
你非常想打耳洞！
- [stammers] You got me!
你猜对了！
[chuckles] - Well...
嗯...
today is your lucky day.
今天是你幸运的一天。
I'm gonna let you get your ears pierced.
我让你去打耳洞。
Right now. - [nervously chuckles]
现在。
Right now, right now? - I knew you'd be so excited!
现在，现在？
- Ooh! Not as excited as I am!
我就知道你会很兴奋！
[mouths words]
[嘴型说话]
[mouthing words]
♪ ♪
[upbeat rock music]
[欢快的摇滚音乐]
- Take the mugs away so we can see your ears.
- 把杯子拿开，这样我们能看到你的耳朵。
- No, come on, don't-- - Just give them to me.
- 不，拜托，别-- - 直接给我。
[laughter]
[笑声]
- Okay. - You know what, Mom?
- 好的。 - 你知道吗，妈妈？
- I really shouldn't be the only one in the family
- 我真的不应该成为家里唯一一个
to get my ears pierced up.
打耳洞的人。
Let's make this a mother/daughter thing.
让我们把这个变成母女之间的事情。
Here, you go first!
来，你先来！
- [gasps] That is really sweet of you,
那真是太贴心了，
but ahh! I think you should go first.
但是啊！我觉得你应该先来。
- Uh, no, really, uh, you...
呃，不，真的，你...
[laughter]
- [squirms] It's daughters before mothers.
那是女儿优先于母亲。
- Uh, no, but everyone knows the saying is...
呃，不，但大家都知道那句话是...
mothers before daughters! [laughter]
母亲优先于女儿！
- [panting] Okay, fine.
好吧，好吧。
Okay. Here we go.
好的，我们开始。
[squirming] - Whoa!
哇！
I think we've hit the mother lobe.
我觉得我们碰到了母体区域。
[laughter]
笑声
- All right, ready? - [squealing]
好的，准备好了吗？
[snaps]
咔嚓声
Huh. That wasn't that bad.
嗯，也没那么糟糕。
- [sighs] Maybe for you.
也许对你来说是这样。
Your lobe broke my piercer.
你的区域弄坏了我的穿刺器。
[laughter] And it didn't even make a dent.
笑声，甚至都没留下痕迹。
[laughter] - Oh.
[笑声] - 哦。
- I'm gonna need Big Jimmy.
- 我需要大吉米。
- Who's Big Jimmy? - Not who...
- 谁是大吉米？ - 不是谁...
What. [laughter]
什么。 [笑声]
- [screams] - Ah, you know what, Mom?
- [尖叫] - 啊，你知道吗，妈妈？
We can always come back another day.
我们可以改天再来。
- Great idea, honey! Let's go-go-go--
- 好主意，亲爱的！我们走-走-走--
[laughter]
[笑声]
- Whoo! Good thing I didn't pull out Huge Jimmy.
- 哇！还好我没叫出巨大吉米。
[laughter]
[笑声]
♪ ♪
- You really think this is gonna work?
你真的认为这会奏效吗？
- We can't find our snake anywhere.
我们找不到我们的蛇了。
We need you to lure him out of hiding.
我们需要你把他从藏身之处引出来。
- But I'm not a snake charmer.
但我不是耍蛇人。
And I think luring things only works in cartoons.
而且我觉得引诱这种事只在卡通里有效。
[laughter]
笑声
- Do you want the cupcakes or not?
你到底要不要这些纸杯蛋糕？
[laughter]
笑声
[playing "Yankee Doodle"]
[演奏《扬基歌》]
♪ ♪
- Look! There he is!
看！他在那儿！
[awing]
哇！
- Get-- - Leg!
抓住-- 腿！
[laughter] - Oh.
笑声 - 哦。
[distant whistling] - That's Dad!
远处口哨声 - 那是爸爸！
- I'm out! [laughter]
我走了！笑声
- Quick, hide him!
快，藏起他！
- Uh... - There, there, there, there.
呃... 那里，那里，那里，那里。
[laughter]
笑声
- Go, go, he's-- Quad boys: [panting]
快走，他来了——四轮小子们：[喘气声]
Quad boys: Hey, Dad! - Hey, boys.
四轮小子们：嘿，爸爸！ - 嘿，孩子们。
I have a... [laughter]
我有一个... [笑声]
surprise for you.
给你们的惊喜。
Something you've wanted for a long time, but, uh,
你们一直想要的，但是，呃，
I never got it because I was...
我从未买过因为我是...
afraid of...
害怕...
[shrieks] snakes!
[尖叫声] 蛇！
[laughter]
[笑声]
- Enjoy!
享受吧！
- Thanks, Dad!
谢谢，爸爸！
Now, how are we going to take care of two snakes?
现在，我们怎么照顾这两条蛇？
- Looks like we only have to worry about one.
看来我们只需要担心一条。
Christopher's missing!
克里斯托弗不见了！
- What? [laughter]
什么？
- Dicky!
迪基！
- Where'd he go?
他去哪儿了？
- [groans] Great!
太好了！
Now we lost two snakes.
现在我们丢了兩条蛇。
- Well, at least we know things can't get any worse.
嗯，至少我们知道情况不会更糟了。
- Guys!
Do these look bad to you?
[all scream]
- They must be infected.
I knew that snake and piercer shouldn't have been
in the same bag.
- Well, lesson learned.
- Guys! Come on! This is really bad!
- Look at the bright side.
At least now things can't get any worse.
[doorbell rings]
[门铃响]
[quads scream]
[四重奏尖叫]
- Okay...
- 好吧...
now things-- - You really need to stop
现在事情-- - 你真的需要停止
saying that. [laughter]
说那句话。[笑声]
- Dawn! What are we gonna do?
- 黎明！我们该怎么办？
- It's almost time for the recital.
- 演出快开始了。
- Yeah, and our errs are all puffay and scarray.
- 是的，而且我们的错误都肿胀且混乱。
[laughter]
[笑声]
- We never should've declared our "Quadpendence."
- 我们根本不应该宣布我们的“四重独立”。
- Okay, everybody, relax.
好的，大家，放松。
All we have to do is just get through this recital
我们只需要设法度过这场演出
without anyone noticing our ears.
不让任何人注意到我们的耳朵。
- How are we gonna do that?
我们该怎么做呢？
- These bonnets don't even cover our ears.
这些软帽甚至遮不住我们的耳朵。
- Well, we're still not giving up.
不过，我们绝不放弃。
Hey!
嘿！
Did our forefathers give up?
我们的先辈们放弃过吗？
No! They fought for our independence.
没有！他们为我们的独立而战。
- Dawn, it's really not the same without the music.
Dawn，没有音乐真的不一样。
- Fine, but we're still not giving up.
- 好吧，但我们仍然没有放弃。
[laughter]
[笑声]
♪ ♪
[clapping]
[鼓掌]
- Welcome, parents, to our Spirit of Independence recital.
- 欢迎各位家长，来到我们的独立精神朗诵会。
Now, as you're about to see, these revolutionary students
现在，正如你们即将看到的，这些革命学生
worked until they were red, white, and blue in the face
为了娱乐你们，他们努力到面红耳赤。
to entertain you. [laughter]
[笑声]
So, I give you your little stars...
所以，我给你们这些小星星...
and stripes. [chuckles]
和条纹。[轻笑]
[clapping]
[鼓掌]
- Mae! Are my ears covered?
- 梅！我的耳朵遮住了吗？
- Shh! You're screaming.
- 嘘！你在尖叫。
- Sorry! I'm swollen inside, too!
- 对不起！我里面也肿了！
I can barely hear.
我几乎听不见。
- Huh? - What?
- 啊？ - 什么？
- I can barly herr.
- 我几乎听不见。
[laughter] - Dawn.
[笑声] - 道恩。
I can't believe we let you talk us into this.
真不敢相信我们让你说服我们做这个。
I mean, we look ridiculous!
我是说，我们看起来太可笑了！
- Yes, yes, the wigs do tickle us.
- 是的，是的，这些假发确实让我们发痒。
[laughter]
[笑声]
[drums rolling]
[鼓声滚动]
["America the Beautiful" playing off-tempo]
[“美丽的美国”以不协调的节奏播放]
♪ ♪
[音乐]
[laughter] - You guys sound way off!
[笑声] - 你们唱得完全不对！
- I know! Aren't we totally pulling this off?
- 我知道！我们不是完全搞定了吗？
[laughter]
[笑声]
- Guys, what is going on? We practiced this!
- 伙计们，这是怎么回事？我们练习过的！
- This is horrible.
- 这太糟糕了。
[laughter]
[笑声]
- At least it can't get any worse!
- 至少不能再糟糕了！
- Shh! [laughter]
- 嘘！[笑声]
[playing clarinet solo]
[吹单簧管独奏]
♪ ♪
[laughter]
[笑声]
- Snake!
- 蛇！
[all screaming]
[所有人尖叫]
- Snake, ahoy! Snake, ahoy!
- 有蛇！有蛇！
He looked right at me!
他正看着我！
- [screaming] [laughter]
[尖叫声] [笑声]
- [squealing]
[吱吱声]
- Told you we have a snake!
我告诉过你们有条蛇！
[laughter]
[笑声]
- [gasps] What happened to your ears?
[喘气声] 你的耳朵怎么了？
- Oh! [chuckles]
哦！[轻笑]
It was the recital of the year!
那是年度表演！
[laughter] - [gasping]
[笑声] - [喘气声]
- [stammers] The boys have a snake!
[结巴] 男孩们有条蛇！
[laughing]
[笑]
♪ ♪
- Wow, this might be the worst infection I have ever seen.
- 哇，这可能是我见过的最严重的感染。
- [shudders] [gagging]
- [颤抖] [作呕]
[laughter]
[笑声]
Oh, there is nowhere to look in this house!
哦，这房子里真没地方可看！
[laughter] - Dad...
[笑声] - 爸爸...
the snake you bought us, which is the only snake...
你给我们买的那条蛇，也是我们家唯一的一条蛇...
- Mm-hmm. - We've ever had in this house,
- 嗯哼。 - 我们家有史以来唯一的一条蛇，
[laughter] is now safe in the terrarium.
[笑声] 现在安全地放在了爬虫箱里。
- I'm sorry, Mom.
- 对不起，妈妈。
I just wanted to get my ears pierced so bad,
我真的很想打耳洞，
but I really shouldn't have done it behind your back.
但我真的不应该在你背后偷偷做这件事。
- Yeah, or in the garage. With a dirty piercer.
- 是的，或者在车库里。用一个脏兮兮的打洞器。
Without adult supervision.
没有成年人的监督。
- Yeah, that too. [laughter]
- 是的，还有这个。
- And I probably shouldn't have stopped you from
- 而且我可能不应该因为害怕就阻止你打耳洞。
getting them pierced just because I was scared.
- 我可能也不应该因为害怕就给你们买了一条蛇。
- And I probably shouldn't have bought you guys a snake
just because I was scared.
- 我可能也不应该因为害怕就给你们买了一条蛇。
[laughter]
- Well, as long as you three learned your lesson.
- 好吧，只要你们三个吸取了教训。
[laughter] - Oh, honey,
[笑声] - 哦，亲爱的，
can you open up the first aid kit and hand me the ointment?
你能打开急救箱，递给我药膏吗？
- Happy to, honey! - Thank you.
- 很乐意，亲爱的！ - 谢谢你。
- Happy to open anything that doesn't have a snake in it.
- 很乐意打开任何没有蛇的东西。
[laughter]
[笑声]
Snake! [squirming]
蛇！ [扭动]
- [squealing] - [screaming]
- [尖叫] - [尖叫]
- Why are there two snakes?
- 为什么有两条蛇？
boys: Uh... Ahhh!
男孩们: 呃... 啊！
[laughter]
[笑声]
♪ ♪
[upbeat rock music]
[欢快的摇滚音乐]
♪ ♪